- It was a nice retirement party.
- I guess.
(Howard:)Still, it's a shame Professor Rothman
was forced to step down.
Well, what choice
did the university have? He snapped.
(Leonard:)It happens to theoretical physicists
all the time.
(Howard:)I wonder how long Sheldon's got.
(Sheldon:)These shrimp are all the same size.
There's no logical order
to eat them in.
(Leonard:)Can't be very long.
(Raj:)Hey, look,
there's Rothman's empty office.
(Raj:)- Sad.
- Yeah.
- lndeed.
- So sad.
(Sheldon:)Dibs.
What's up, fellas?
(Sheldon:)What are you doing here, Kripke?
Measuring my new office for drapes.
(Sheldon:)This is not your office.
It hasn't been assigned yet.
l called dibs at Christmas when
Rothman tried to have intercourse...
(Kripke:)...with the Toys for Tots
collection box.
(Sheldon:)Offices are not assigned
because someone called dibs.
- You just called dibs.
- Shut it.
(Sheldon:)Offices are assigned by seniority.
l arrived at the university first.
l arrived at the office first.
I'm the proverbial early bird.
(Sheldon:)- Gentlemen.
- Mr. Rothman.
(Howard:)- Professor Rothman.
- Professor Rothman.
(Rothman:)Good evening.
- See you.
(Raj:)I'm glad
that men are wearing hats again.
(Raj:)They're so distinguished.